

# ROKAS KLIUČINSKAS

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

### **CONTACT**

Kaunas, Lithuania

+370 69197232

rokasklkl@gmail.com

mokas.netlify.app

### SOCIAL NETWORKS

f rokas.kliucinskas

in rokas-kliučinskas

**k**liucis

Rokaskl

## **LANGUAGE**

LITHUANIAN • • • •

ENGLISH • • • •

RUSSIAN • • • • •

## **HOBBIES**

Music Photography

Travelling Chess



## **ABOUT ME**

Hi! I am Rokas Kliučinskas, a web designer/developer focused on creating great web experiences from Kaunas Lithuania. Designing and coding have been my passion since the days I started working with computers but I found myself into web design/development since 2017. Beside coding, I am interested in photography, music production and I also love to travel.



#### **EDUCATION**

> LSMU GYMNASIUM

SEP 2013- JUNE 2017

Kaunas (Lithuania)

> COMPUTER SCIENCE

SEP 2017 - PRESENT

Kaunas University of Technology, Kaunas (Lithuania)

#### > NFQ CODING ACADEMY

OCT 2019 - DEC 2019

NFQ, Kaunas (Lithuania)

- Back-End (Php, Symfony)
- Front-End (JS, JSX, CSS, HTML, React)
- DB (MySQL)
- UX



## **EXPERIENCE**

> BICYCLE SHOP MANAGER

JUNE 2016 - SEP 2016

UAB "GUZE", Kaunas (Lithuania)

> WAREHOUSE WORKER

JUNE 2018- SEP 2018

Hobij BV, Waalwijk (Netherlands)



**REACT** 

#### **SKILLS**

HTML	C#	FIGMA
CSS	PYTHON	PHOTOSHOP
SCSS	PHP	ILLUSTRATOR
JS	SYMFONY	UML
JSX	.NET	